Hey, it's
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): Congressman Andy Levin sitting in my office this morning with my new friend Peter Morley who is doing as much as any person in this country to fight for health care for every person and right now our focus is on protecting people with pre-existing
Speaker 2: conditions.
Speaker 2: which is super important to both of us, personally.
Speaker 3 (lower-pitched voice): - Yes, yes, I, as I was telling you, I have over 10 pre-existing conditions and I live with lupus, I'm a two-time cancer survivor, and it's a big struggle for me every day. It's a struggle for me to get down to DC, but I'm happy to do it and I'm happy to fight it. I'm happy to represent the stories because 130 million people with pre-existing conditions
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): are at stake.
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): So this isn't a time to be quiet. Yeah, so Peter's voice and the voice of everybody seeing this, who has a pre-existing condition, yourself, your kids, your parents, your aunts and uncles, we need you to tell your members of Congress that we cannot allow this lawsuit to go forward that would completely overturn
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): the Affordable Care Act, and we need to fight to support these bills that we're trying to pass in the House. We've already passed some. We will pass more that protect people with pre-existing conditions, like my two older kids, Kobe and Saul. Thank you, Congressman. Thank you for everything that you're doing. I really appreciate it. Thank you. Thanks for coming in. He's got 13 meetings today. I mean, come on. This is awesome. Thank you so
much for
Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): what you're doing. Seriously. I appreciate it. This is the best. This is America. This is why I'm here, is to get to meet people like you. It's such a privilege. Thank
you.